Inshallah the boy
called me your sister-in-law Bau Boli
and then the plethora of
poddas
we will not go knowing that I will do it
because a Gujarati man is
not afraid of anyone's father except his own wife
Amazingly talented person Vishal Jethwa
started how was
Vadodara you yesterday
how was the
filmfare very good you were not nominated this year you will be nominated next year you will not
get nominated award
kya baat achcha je kolo na na konno konno na
You are doing roles like brother villain to such friendly friend, your range
is amazing, I think
you have also played the role of Akbar in Maharana Pratap, my mother used to
say that you should not trust a manjri eyed person, after
watching Mardaani 2 and Maharana Pratap, I felt my
mother's words were true, but then I have
not seen Home Bound yet, but after watching the trailer, it
seems that you will change the definition,
yes, earlier everyone used to say to me that if this manjri eyed person is complete, then
this will be very low,
meaning, some had tak ye baat sah bhi hai [laughter]
But you are Gujarati and you carry the badge of being a
Gujarati even to Kan even to different countries that you have been a part of during the
Home Bound journey, then from there I
discovered that you are actually
Gujarati and when we talk about Gujarati folk and
culture, there are so many Gujaratis, I
think  I want to say something to all the Gujaratis
of
Actually Thank you Thank you Let's
talk about Gujarati A mother comes from a shayari
Yes, there is
one for Gujaratis and the
sun does not bow to anyone The
mountain does not bow to anyone The sun does
not bow to anyone The mountain does not bow to anyone
I am proud to be a Gujarati because a
Gujarati man is not afraid of anyone's father except his own wife
Brother, this is a brainwashed man Ha Brother, this is it
[laughter]
Sharp Sharp Boy
Vishal Yaar Thank you Thank you But actually
you know I have seen that in this can
and all the other places what am I doing with Hindi that I sing
all things Gujarati folk
because I felt that
even though some people know Gujarati people in Bollywood, but
songs are our Gujarati culture, our Gujarati
folk diaries and all this is so rich and there are
so many variations in it that I feel that I should
reach these people and
so many people have given me space in Bollywood and
If I can promote this and make some small
contribution, why not? That's why
I try, all
brothers must do it, because the more famous you
become, the more views you will get on the episode, so
[laughter] Be brave,
yes, and then maybe if everyone has come to the show, Diarra can
also earn money back. These many
fans are now increasing very slowly,
because all the
projects back to back and every project somehow got a hit in the
news like Home Bound, then
people immediately started searching for it, saying, "
Come on, this picture gets fans, you get them on the road,
and you get many fans of different types,
brother, one of those fans is a man, and
I am in a marriage, what did I do in a marriage?
A brother came to me and came to me and said, "Hey,
brother, he gave me his phone like this, I said, "
One meter, what does one beat mean?" Then
I had to decode it, that
after one beat, I got a little  After some time I decoded it, one click
means click, okay, then I
took the phone like this, I sat here, I clicked like this,
then I took the phone and another click,
[Laughter]
I Akshay I Akshay I Akshay I Akshay please please yes yes
He pulled someone else's hair in so many pictures
[Laughter] Hey hey
My smile is perfect for a second, in the
10th second someone gets
elbowed in the head and my face looks like this, and that's the same photo
I take the next day, I take it with me,
Vishal Jethwa [laughter]
In the Oscars, I think Lagaan was the
last movie that went to the Best International Feature
Film category, it reached the point where it was
nominated, it reached the point where it reached this, it didn't reach
RRR didn't
reach
RRR, that music is not in the Best Feature Film, so what do you
think, what are the chances of Home Bound, what is the
last, what is the
last, it didn't reach it, it was just an official
entry, so from
all the pictures from India, our
jury felt that if we send this picture,
then the Oscars people will like it,
but they say that after the nominations, there must have been a
B after Lagaan, but we did
n't have a final after Lagaan.
Keep the nomination attached because it is more of a loss now than it is when
people abuse us after editing and then leave and then feel
uneducated.
So maybe
what do you think, Homebound, if it reaches the final nomination,
if your serious answer on this matter is that the
film definitely has potential. The film
works on such an important issue of India. This is a very
important film.
We talk about discrimination and we
talk about our own acceptance.
We often
cannot accept our identity. As the years go by, we do not realize
that we
also have the issue of accepting our identity. So I think it is a universal topic
and often what happens is that
when a film is an official entry from India, there are
many
points of view or what work this film has done that could have been a
better film. This time
I saw that no one has talked about Homebound related. So I think it is a universal topic and what happens when a film is an official entry from India?  It
seems that it is a very important
film and now how much will it sell?
Now it is sold. Maybe I think and
if I am a greedy person, let me
tell you one thing. Sorry for interrupting.
The best thing is, do you know about Home Bound?
Its executive producer is
Martin Scorsese? If
anyone doesn't know,
who knows Martin Scorsese? Let
me ask him. Do you know
what the public today knows?
Martin Scorsese, you idiot.
Martin Scorsese
lives beyond Vidyanagar. [Laughter] Then
I know that I have
seen Wolf of Wall Street.
Yes, I have
seen some scenes from it.
Yes,
[Laughter] I have
not seen the film.
This is the EP of Home Bound. And that is the movie. All the more special. That is just
fantastic.
And you know how I think.
I think that we deserve it and we should
get it only then. Only then will we have fun. So I
pray that.  Only the best film gets the Oscar
and I also pray that our film is the
best. Wow wow
[applause] So cool. You were so lazy in
school today. [laughter]
Or you were naughty in school, then you gradually became lazy.
Where did you like schooling? Where did you go?
I did my schooling in Gujarati medium schools in
two or three different places. One
in Malad was till the sixth standard.
After that, we shifted to Mirabhaindar.
Okay,
there were two or three
Gujarati medium schools in Mumbai.
Yes, Gujarati medium schools are the same.
My parents told me that I only have fun in Gujarati.
That's why I have English in my ears.
Wherever I go, I can speak English.
English is my good of the good of the
better way of the under
going for the creation
of the parliament.  demutzationfor
the fac of thevirtualvd going under
the time you are doing right the way
my friend
inshallah inshallah the boy played well the
joke took
me apart come on I am saying this is
Vishal Jethwa and I am saying this Jai
Shri Krishna then voice play [laughter] wow wow
brother this is so loud
this English should be said in the ear brother just
out [laughter] loud it is the
very the
baba english show
you both how will you cross the
immigration sorry
padancross the fish
line of immigration you can
ofang meera malad
meet me and tell me this
friendly bossy [laughter]
[laughter]
psychological
pundit auditoyam
[Laughter]
It turns out that our subtitler must have gone crazy in putting subtitles in this
[Laughter] What are you guys talking about
subtitles in
English because my English is some
Gujarati sleeping in it [Laughter]
Lapsing and setting then the
plethora of
podda
My English teacher used to tell me to mind
your tongue like this Mind your tongue and
Gujarati
uncles' English is the best That
day after a show an uncle came to me and said
that Monbhai is in the US I had also gone a
little in between US Canada everything
keeps talking International He has
booked tickets for Updown So [Laughter]
You have booked tickets so you shopper is
not giving you
this Yes Yes Yes Because we are the promoters
We have organized it Anyways If
I was talking then that uncle came  Which
side was Kanedi Katke on? Monbhai, your program is so
strong and oh, the tune is amazing. The
word-of-mouth publicity of your program is
so good. I said, where did this publicity happen? I
also want to do it. Yes, Manubhai, I
said, it is called word of mouth. No, mouth-to-
mouth. In
Kansam, you call it Kan. Can
or Kan.
We will not go. I will do it.
We sell grasshoppers in Ahmedabad and Mumbai.
[Laughter]
Vishal, in the media interview that he had,
you sang Chapakaru. If something happens here today
for the audience of Baroda, it will be really strong. Let's
try. If there is a fumble in the middle,
please cut it.
Yes, otherwise, we will do a retake. What is it?
I like Dior very much and many people
ask me that Vishalbhai, you who work in Bollywood and
live in Mumbai, Diors who do
not know how to do Chapakaru, then
I will tell them.  I say this, the great Jatajut
Chandrabhal Ganga Ki
Tarang Mal Vimal Neer Gaje Harlochan Teh Red
Red Sandalwood Ki Khori Bal Kumkum Sindoor Rose Bhrgati
Varsaje Mundan Ki Kanthamal Vihasarat Harday Kujal
Crystal Jal Rudramal Hardayal Raache Hey Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam Bam
Damrubaj Naad Ved Swar Suraj Bhole
Maharaj Aaj Tandav Naache Raji Re Shankar Maharaj
Aaj Tandav Naache But what kind of Tandav Jatatvi Galat Jal Prasad
Pavithsthale Gale Valamblaanta Bhujang Tunga Malikam Dum Dum Dum
Damnadamravayam
Chakar Chand Tandav Tanotunshivshivam
Jataktaah Sambhrambhramlimpanarjari
Villolavichavallari  The seated Murdhani Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Dhagat Jawallat
Patpavke Kishore Chandrasekhar Prati
Pratikshan Mam Dharadharendra Nandini Vilas Bandhu Bandura Suratrigant Santati
Pramodmanman Se Kripa Kataksha Gorani
Nirudra Durdarapatidi Pe Digambare Mano Vinod Metu Vastu Ni Vinod Metu Vastu Ni Vinod Metu Vastu Parvati Pate Har Har
Mahadev Har
Shambhu Vishal Jee Vishal Jee Dhabhad Jees
Abhe Chhapra Phaal Abhe
Bhai Clap For Vishal Everybody Vishal
Thank you very much for watching this video Keep supporting like this Loveri Keep
giving love and keep subscribing
so that we reach 1 million
and take membership Yaar How many times do you apply
Live shows are limited so
keep looking in the comments for the link
and jami  If you have taken it, don't forget to wash your hands.